Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting,
either will I'm feeling alive,
look out below, wake up sunshine,
here we go.
Raise your flag up high,
hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky, time
to journey on, on your mark.
Come aboard with me.
We're on Earth, a legendary!.
If you can show your breath?
Then we'll make some waves!.
We run our daunted!.
Ain't no beginners!.
Cause if you're wanted?
Then you're a winner!.
For we are on the cruise!.
And freedom is the only rule!.
Fearless night and day!.
Cause that's just our way!.
Find one piece!.
I'll be the first!.
I've heard it be so bad just at first!.
It's all this real!.
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel!.
I'm done playing, feel it's waiting!.
In the world I'm feeling alive!.
But I'll be loud!.
Wake up sunshine, here we go!.
We have come so far!.
Gotta make it to the end!.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!.
I've always got your back, my friend!.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward!.
Dreaming from the very first
day, I'd make my name!.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed!.
I'm done playing through with the wave!.
In the world I'm feeling
alive, look out below!.
Wake up, sunshine!.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!.
We go!.
In the decade that followed,
the remaining members of the royal
family, including the king himself,?
rarely left the palace,
but chose to speak to the nation
through their monitors instead.
And all the while, the islander's
signature steadily replenished.
So there you have it.
That's how we spent the past 16
years fighting discrimination.
And that's how the Fishman
Pirates were formed and divided.
There's no denying the awful
things Arlong did to your home.
Even so, at one time, he
was like a brother to me.
When we received news of his violent actions
we took it upon ourselves to stop him.
But he always managed to
dodge any real consequence.
He hid his actions from the navy by
bribing any soldiers that he came across.
I let him live and in failing to stop
him I too share the guilt for his crimes.
If you're so sorry kill yourself.
Sanji take responsibility pay with your
life for the suffering that you caused her.
Give her peace that's
enough Sanji what are you
serious Nami how could
you excuse the things they
Did to you I'll never
excuse what Arlong did
but Jinbei he never meant
for anyone to get hurt.
I will accept any punishment if you
wish for me to take my own life drop it.
Look it's okay.
The only one I hate is Arlong.
Believe me I'm relieved to hear you're
not the mastermind of the Arlong Pirates.
And you're a friend of Luffy's
which tells me plenty about you.
I won't lie.
The Arlong Pirates made
my life a living hell.
But you know if it wasn't for that
nightmare I never would have met my friends.
That awful time made me who I am I can't
hate you just because you're a fish man.
So you you don't get to pity
me just because of my past.
I'm fine with my past because
I'm happy in the present.
It doesn't matter who did
this to me don't become angry.
not on my behalf.
Please you can't tell anyone on the island
the tragedy that we've endured?
and our hatred must die with us.
I wouldn't dwell on it.
There's nothing you could have done.
You've known each other
since childhood, after all.
Like him or not, he's still like a
brother to you and you're no killer.
I don't deserve to be treated so kindly.
You have my gratitude.
You... Nami.
You're a good man, Jinpei.
I know how hard it is to be a big brother.
You're a hell of a guy, Jinbei!
That whole story?
I like them all so much!
Tiger and Odashime!
Shut your mouth, Franky!
He must have been carrying so much pain.
Luffy?
What?
Moron. Wake up!
I didn't need that nap.
So?
Jinbei, what did the queen?
end up doing to that beast you got?
Are you for real?
You mean you fell asleep at the
very beginning of the story?
Did I miss it all?
You did!
Shirahoshi, right?
You gonna be okay?
Nami-chin!
She's royalty!
Don't be so casual, please!
Oh, forgive me for being so emotional.
It's difficult not to cry
when I think about my mother.
She sounds like she was quite the woman.
Yes.
It's a real pleasure
to meet you, Nami-chin.
No, princess!
Nami-chin is just a silly nickname I gave
her, so it's just plain Nami, no chin!
Excuse me,
perhaps it's a bit
forward of me to say this,
but even though we just met,
I feel a connection to you,
like we've been friends for a long time.
Oh yeah?
Well, we've both been through
some similar rough patches.
Excuse me, I just lost track of time.
I need to know what the
situation is at the Ryugu Palace.
Just to confirm what you've told me,
Heart and his crew have taken the
King and the Palace Guards captive.
Apart from that, you're not sure what
happened to three members of your crew.
And that's all the
information we have, correct?
You...
Hey, Jinbei, if the siege is
playing out as Heart planned,
there's a good chance the rest of the
country is falling to his forces now, too.
Hold on.
Are you saying you know what his plan is?
To be honest,
I have had my suspicions he was up to
something ever since he retired from the army.
But he was clever enough to
keep the details hidden from me.
Not me, I know.
But first, let me warn you.
Heart hates humans even
more than Arlong did.
The only thing driving him is resentment.
He talks about rebuilding the kingdom,
but all he really wants to do
is cause suffering to humans.
And to prove my point, you'll see there's
one big difference between him and Arlong.
Arlong had no problem with killing humans,
but the one thing he'd never
do is hurt other fishmen.
Heart, he doesn't care.
He'll also turn his fury against
fishmen who are sympathetic to humans.
He'll cut down anyone in his way.
The World Summit is set
to take place again soon,
but a lot's changed in
the last four years.
For the first time since Odohime's death,
they've actually gathered enough
signatures for King Neptune to
speak at the summit about relocating
Fishman Island to the surface.
Hmm.
I see.
Then Hortius seized the
palace just for that? I wish.
No, I'm afraid it's a lot worse than that.
What?
What is that?
It's huge!
Think it's that big?
What the?
It's a video transponder snail.
What's it doing out here?
Look! It's activated!
Oh yeah, it's projecting!
On the bubble!
Hmm, I thought so.
It's him.
What's up?
You know that guy?
That's Heart.
This can't be good.
He found us? Hodges!
Hello there, people of Fishman Island.
Am I coming through?
Well then,
for those of you who don't know, I'm
the captain of the new Fishman Pirates.
My name is Heart Jones!
Come on! Next!
Next!
You won't step on it!
I'm sure Queen Otohime would forgive us.
If I refused, it would kill me.
I can't believe this is happening.
I'm sorry, Queen Otohime.
I don't want to.
There you go.
Next.
How boring.
No one's even trying to resist.
People are stomping on her
without a second thought.
Hey, Drum.
You've got to come see this quick.
Captain Horty's live on the air.
So he's the one behind
all this. The bastard.
Why does he want us to
stuff on the queen so bad?
Wait, that guy?
Wasn't he also the soldier from the plaza?
He killed Otsuhime's assassin that day.
That's right.
His name is Heart Jones. The same guy.
Why would one of that team
soldiers do such a thing?
There's something every citizen of
the Ryugu kingdom needs to know.
This will be destroyed. And quickly.
We'll rebuild it from scratch.
But with a new king.
Like me.
What's he talking about?
Who does he think he is? Screw you!
This is crazy!
Where is this broadcast even coming from?
King Neptune?
Is he okay?
The Straw Hat supposedly
took over the palace.
Do you think they're his allies?
Nothing makes sense anymore!
I will usher in a new era for?
Fishman Island.
For starters, we'll end all
friendly relations with humans.
In place of the sympathizers,
those loyal to our cause will
move in from the Fishman District.
They hate humans too.
And will do whatever it takes to?
rid this country of them.
So treat them with respect.
Is he serious? New residents?
He's just gonna let all these criminals
roam free through our kingdom?
You still love her, don't you?
Otohime, our most cherished queen.
She was indeed selfless
and worked tirelessly
to build a bridge between
fishmen and humans.
I do respect her spirit.
But have you forgotten
the end of her tale?
She was killed by a no-man Even if you
approach them with a pure heart and
kind intentions They'll just take
advantage of you and leave you in the dirt
We have to wake up, can't you see?
Woody
Sorry, but the royal family's
been duping you for years.
If we follow them, we'll face extinction.
As long as humans exist, the
Skull of Harmony is unattainable.
It's a pipe dream that's been
perpetuated for far too long.
Stop it.
See for yourself.
They have father.
How could they? Father!
Not the king.
King Neptune got old.
It happens to everyone.
The only way to advance is
to eliminate the old god,
so they won't hold us back anymore.
Huh.
When you think about it, this
mess is kind of our fault.
If we hadn't shown up,
the king might be fine.
More like Zoro's fault.
What in the world did
you do at the palace?
Jinbei, wait! Calm down!
A bunch of Neptune soldiers attacked
Namichin and her friends first!
They were just trying
to defend themselves!
As you may have figured out by now,
I am at the Ryugu Palace, and there's
something else I want to show you.
This here is from the nobles.
The queen risked her life for this.
Ten years ago, that is.
If I destroy this letter, it's over.
You won't get another one.
Along with that,
here we have a box
with signatures from
most of Fishman Island.
Frankly, I'm disgusted by the numbers.
Who in their right mind would want to
befriend humans after all they've done?
So, if your name is on
any of these, thank you.
I know who I have to weed out.
My kingdom will be better without you.
And with that in mind,
why don't we get started?
Here's page one.
Enough stepping on pictures. That's true.
It's far too easy to pretend you don't
mind doing it just to save yourselves.
But these signatures,
they give me concrete evidence of who
I can suspect will oppose my rule?
It's like you signed
your own death warrant!
All right then, let's
see who the traitors are.
Also, before I go
Strat, I know you're there
I have something that
may be of interest to you
As you watch from wherever
you are I want you to
know that this is just the
beginning of my revenge!
For what you did to Arlong?
Enjoy.
Oh man, he even captured Zoro?
That's what we get, leaving
them alone But still, all three?
Do it. Right.
Do it.
Oh no, what's this? We're going up.
This can't possibly be good.
Well, yes, now what?
Something's coming.
It's water!
By the time we finish the king's execution,
that room will be completely flooded.
You know the humans can't survive
that, if I'm not mistaken.
Too bad.
Straw Hat, Luffy!
Look at that bounty!
Four hundred million!
The heads of you and your
crewmates will serve as
a perfect warning to any
humans who dare defy us!
But for now, we're tearing
down the old Ryugu kingdom!
We're done with the failures of the past.
This is the time for revolution!
Just three hours, that's all we need.
Fishman Island will take back
its pride in three hours!
Ja-ha-ha-ha-ha!
We can't stay!
We shall stop them!
Hey guys!
This water isn't getting any lower! Oh no!
Oh, I just got dry, too.
Now let's all figure out a way to save me.
Or better yet, save us!
Do you have any ideas?
Any day? I'm thinking.
First, get me out of these chains.
You got it!
Psychic powers, don't fail me now!
Chains come off!
Your links are getting looser.
The metal's getting weaker.
Chains be gone!
Nothing.
Well, we're stuck.
Nice knowing you guys.
I still can't stop laughing.
Did you see the look on those
fishmen's faces when I stood up?
Priceless.
Poor guy was probably adrift at sea.
I can't help but feel sorry for him.
It looks like he died a long time ago.
Rackle!
I did die.
He's alive somewhat well I may
do at least the name's brook
we're all gonna die we wouldn't
have gotten caught if it
weren't for you please help
they're killing me wait never
mind you're killing me too well
at least nami and the others
escaped soon luffy and the
rest of the crew will come
get us out of here wishful
thinking what if they don't as
robin would say oh i hope
nami hasn't been eaten by some
deep sea creature
this
poneglyph
is different from the others
let's see it looks like a
letter as well as an apology
but who is this apology for and why
did you engrave it in stone joy boy
hey that's a lot of money
400 million where did
they go up huh no one
cares about your bounty
Obviously, they're using
the others as bait.
Think about it, Luffy.
You're infamous now.
The conflict at Marineford
made sure of that.
Once you surpass 300 million,
it rarely increases again.
Well, anyway, if someone wants
to fight me, I'll fight them.
I beg you, don't act rashly.
They have father.
My father needs me!
I have to help!
I'm coming, Daddy!
Megalo!
I can't just stay here!
Come back! Shura Hachi!
Megalo, don't move!
You could die!
If I don't save father, maybe...
I do understand the urgency,
but please, you must listen.
You...
he's right.
You can't go back right now.
You too?
The one person that Heart is most afraid
of in the Ryugu kingdom is you, princess.
Your power.
Even if Heart does change the island to
suit his needs, you'll still be a threat.
If you summon the sea kings, everything
will come crashing down in an instant.
That's why he took King Neptune hostage,
to neutralize the princess
and to lure her back.
You're saying this whole time, they've
really been after Shirahoshi? You.
Yes, but not in the way you might think.
Heart doesn't want to capture
the princess to use her power.
This may sound cruel, but he'd prefer
a threat like her not exist at all.
That's why he partnered
with Vander Decken.
Deccan is capable of killing
her, plain and simple.
He'll destroy anything
that stands in his way.
Hmm.
That's right.
Heart wants the princess
to rush into the plaza.
There, she would be most vulnerable.
Um, my family has mentioned my power
before, but I'm afraid that's all.
Even if you were to ask me to
communicate with the Sea Kings,
I don't think I could do it.
Not now.
To be honest, I'm not convinced that
I have the power in the first place.
Whether you do or not, Heart has no
qualms with killing you just to be safe.
Therefore, we must not let him find out
that you aren't able to control the power.
The more afraid of you he is,
the better things are for us.
All right.
Are you done? Good.
Then I'm going.
Hey, Shark, take me back to the palace.
I'm leaving the crybaby
with you. That cool?
Hell yeah.
Luffy, I told you to wait.
Huh?
You don't get it.
You people have no
business fighting Heart.
What's the big deal, huh?
We can't fight because
we're humans, is that it?
It doesn't make sense when you two say it.
Quit complicating things.
That's right.
This battle isn't for you.
If you win, the surviving fishmen
will go on hating humans again.
Please, allow me to handle it.
I can't.
Not when my crew is in trouble.
It's not that I don't trust you.
This fight is personal for me, too.
You guys...
They're both right.
Stay out of this. Wait here.
Not a chance.
Such a stubborn fool.
Just shut up already.
I said I'm going.
Stop me if you can.
Lucy.
Since we were allies before, I had
hoped that you would honor my request.
How easily I forget who you are?
Hard-headedness truly
does run in your family.
If you're not going to listen
to me, I have no choice!
Please, you two, try to calm down.
Luffy, Jinbei,
this is no time for you guys to act
like you're going to kill each other.
Get out of my way, I
gotta go save my friends.
And when I'm done, I'm
kicking Horty's ass.
I told you not to get
involved with him, Luffy.
Whoa, hey, surely there's a
better way to work this out?
Yeah, stop it, both of you.
Luffy, please, I don't
want my friends to fight.
Shark, let's go, get
me back to the palace.
You have to go through me first!
Right, fine by me!
Miss Man Caratter, the Shark Brickfish!
What? Oh no!
That looks bad!
That...
That hurt. What? No way.
He's made of rubber.
Attacks like that
shouldn't even work on him.
But this is Fishman Karate, a
form based on manipulating water.
I can send shockwaves through vapor in the
air until they finally
find my target's body.
Seeing as every living
creature is made up of water,
not even a rubber man
can escape the impact.
Bring it!
You shall not pass, Wave!
Second gear!
Now come, come!
After so much training, don't
tell me that's all you've got!
Not a chance!
Enough of that.
You're back.
Hey get out of the way now!
Move it you'll die!
Don't worry I'll save you.
There's no need to fight.
I'm sure you both have your
reasons, but you're friends, right?
Wait, you mean Robin's been in
the forest this entire time?
Well, good luck, you guys!
Wait a damn second!
You're just gonna leave
without explaining or anything?
Since when have you been able to
do something like this freaky crap?
It's a new trick.
I was surprised.
It first happened on my world
tour as Soul King quite suddenly.
Well, it's actually pretty
obvious when you think about it.
If a man can go anywhere undetected, there's
one thing he's going to go looking for.
He's so lucky, Zoro.
Why can't I be dead like he is? Really?
Well, it's about time we
got this show underway.
Do you want some of us to stay and protect
the palace while you're gone, Boss Heart?
No need.
What don't you remember?
No one else can get
through the palace gate.
We'll Station a handful
of men here to make
sure someone's around to
open it when I Return.
After all, you can't
lock out the new king.
More like nonsense.
You will Never be respected as
king if you rule through violence.
Is that really what you?
I don't want your last words to be.
I'd have gone for something strong.
Ah.
My scar, it's burning.
I can't believe that the stupid human
swordsman actually managed to cut me.
Ah, it's wearing off.
Hey, it's time for my next dose. Right.
Now I feel as good as new.
Isn't the dangerous
taking that much at once?
I thought so. Hey, Captain.
What do we do with the three
Straw Hats we captured?
Nothing.
They're just humans.
They'll drown if left alone.
And the palace is secure,
so no one will be able to rescue
them regardless of who comes.
Forget them. Now,
what's the current status
of the residents from
the Fishman district
that we recruited today?
They're doing just fine.
In fact, they should be
making their move as we speak.
That's good.
Pretty soon they'll be out of the slums.
Seeing as once all of the
traders have left or been killed,
there'll be plenty of
houses on the market.
Then our country will finally be united
in its hatred for the pathetic human race.
I think I found it, guys.
A bright ray of hope.
Listen, those fishermen we were
dealing with earlier have left,
so the palace is completely empty.
Or rather, it would be if they
hadn't left Papagu behind.
That's awesome, Brook.
Now we just need to ask Papagu to find
the keys to get us out of these chains.
I guess we need the one
to unlock this cage too.
Don't be an idiot.
Just find one of my swords.
That's all we really need to escape.
I'll cut anything in my way. Yeah.
That's all you ever want to do.
I need your help!
Find the keys, please!
No, wait! The sword! Yeah,
yeah! Go find the sword!
Go away!
I don't know what you're talking about!
What are you doing? That's not me!
Think, Luffy.
Have you considered
what will happen if you
resort to violence
while on Fishman Island?
Every time my people have tried to reach
out and open their hearts to humans,
They have been met with nothing
but disappointment and prejudice.
Humans like to make us suffer.
Humans hate fishmen.
They look down on us. Don't you see?
This is what our citizens
have come to believe because
of the horrible things that
have happened in our past.
And Arlong is a perfect example.
The people here believe that
the humans hunted him when
he went to the surface solely
because he was a fishman.
And now you, the people who
suppressed Arlong are here.
What will the islanders think
if you crush Heart as well?
Misguided though he may be, Horty's
aim is to fight against persecution.
So even if it saves us from
this crisis in the long run?
If they see a group of
humans attacking him,
it will only solidify the idea that
things will never change between us.
Oh well that's too bad you're crazy
if you think we won't rescue our crew?
And unless we do something soon Horty's
going to take over the whole island!
And that's a problem because we have
a lot of friends that live here.
Like Hachi yeah you've kept pretty
quiet about who banged you up so bad.
But now that I think about
it you mentioned before that
Heart attacks any fish man
that sympathizes with humans
so i guess the reason you're
in that sorry state is because
you spoke up for us right
why is that true already did
this to you i can't say jimbae
with all that in mind i'm
pretty sure luffy wants to
fight so bad because this is
your home too we won't be
able to leave the island like
this we can't turn a blind
eye there's too much at stake
we're taking a stand.
It's the mermaid paradise
I've always dreamed of!
Get out of my way, Team Bay.
I won't let you keep me here anymore.
Let me handle it.
You stay put.
Shut up!
Stop!
Sanji said all that cool stuff
and you still want to fight?
If that is what it takes to
make you listen to me, yes!
What did you say?
Ugh, knock it off.